New Mexico Folklife Project collection, 1984-1985
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Graphic materials, 1984-1985
  - Garcia ranch, buildings and windmill, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico, August 30, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-15)
  - Garcia ranch, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico, August 30, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-16)
  - Garcia ranch, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico, August 30-31, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-17)
  - Pacheco ranch house, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico; Building described as Penitente morada, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico, August 31, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-18)
  - Building described as Penitente morada, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico; Pacheco ranch buildings and water reservoir, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico, August 31, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-19)
  - Pacheco ranch buildings, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico; Cordova ranch, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico, August 31, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-20)
  - Cordova ranch, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico; Erma Trujillo interview, Mosquero, New Mexico, August 31, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-21)
  - Erma Trujillo and Pat Trujillo house, Mosquero, New Mexico; Photos from Margarito Garcia's and Trinidad Garcia's family album, Mosquero, New Mexico, August 31, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-22)
  - At home and studio of Felix Lopez, La Mesilla, New Mexico, June 22, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C001)
  - At home and studio of Felix Lopez, La Mesilla, New Mexico, June 22, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C002)
  - Felix Lopez, artist, at home and studio, La Mesilla, New Mexico; San Francisco de Asis Mission Church, Rancho de Taos New Mexico, June 22-23, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C003)
  - Our Lady of the Rosary Mission Church, Truchas, New Mexico; Chapel built by Eulogio Ortega and painted by Zoraida Ortega, Velarde, New Mexico, June 23, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C004)
  - Eulogio Ortega at his chapel and workshop, Velarde, New Mexico, June 23, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C005)
  - Horacio Valdez's home and workshop, Dixon, New Mexico, June 23, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C006)
  - La Galeria de Colores, preparing for an exhibition, Las Vegas, New Mexico, June 24, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C007)
  - La Galeria de Colores, preparing for an exhibition, Las Vegas, New Mexico; Historic mill, La Cueva, Mora County, New Mexico, June 24, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C008)
  - San Rafael Mission church, La Cueva, Mora County, New Mexico, June 24, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C009)
  - Historical buildings and neighborhood, Mora, New Mexico, June 25, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C010)
  - Historical buildings and neighborhood, Mora, New Mexico; Pop Shaffer Hotel and Rancho Bonito, Mountainair, New Mexico, June 25, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C011)
  - Pop Shaffer Hotel and Rancho Bonito, Jackie and Herman Hudgeons, Mountainair, New Mexico, June 25-26, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C012)
  - Pop Shaffer Hotel, Harding Kayser and Joe Brazil, Mountainair, New Mexico, June 25-26, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 35 mm color slide (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C013)
  - Chapel built by Eulogio Ortega and painted by Zoraida Ortega, Velarde, New Mexico, June 23, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in. color transparency (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C014)
  - Eulogio Ortega's workshop and home chapel, Velarde, New Mexico, June 23, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in. color transparency (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C015)
  - Home of Horacio Valdez, Dixon, New Mexico; Pop Shaffer Hotel, Mountainair, New Mexico, June 23-26, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in. color transparency (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C016)
  - Pop Shaffer Hotel, Harding Kayser and Joe Brazil, Mountainair, New Mexico, June 26, 1984, Carl Fleischhauer; 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in. color transparency (Item-id AFC 1991/032: CF-C017)
  - Scenes in Clayton, New Mexico; Town-center businesses, Mosquero, New Mexico, August 28-30, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in. color transparency (Item-id AFC 1991/032: C-23)
  - Town-center businesses and Garcia family home, Mosquero, New Mexico; Garcia ranch house, Mosquero Canyon, New Mexico, August 30, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in. color transparency (Item-id AFC 1991/032: C-24)
  - St. Joseph's Roman Catholic Church and other scenes in and near Mosquero, New Mexico, August 30, 1985, Carl Fleischhauer; 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in. color transparency (Item-id AFC 1991/032: C-25)